import { QuestionData } from './types';

export const questions: QuestionData[] = [
  {
    number: 1,
    answered: true,
    question: 'Which country is Kuala Lumpur the capital',
    selectedAnswer: 2,
    answers: [],
  },
  {
    number: 2,
    question: 'Which country is Kuala Lumpur the capital 2',
    selectedAnswer: null,
    answers: ['1', '2', '3', '4'],
    correctAnswer: 2,
  },
  {
    number: 3,
    answered: false,
    question: 'Which country is Kuala Lumpur the capital',
    selectedAnswer: null,
    answers: [],
  },
  {
    number: 4,
    answered: false,
    question: 'Which country is Kuala Lumpur the capital',
    selectedAnswer: null,
    answers: [],
  },
  {
    number: 5,
    answered: false,
    question: 'Which country is Kuala Lumpur the capital',
    selectedAnswer: null,
    answers: [],
  },
  {
    number: 6,
    answered: false,
    question: 'Which country is Kuala Lumpur the capital',
    selectedAnswer: null,
    answers: [],
  },
  {
    number: 7,
    answered: false,
    question: 'Which country is Kuala Lumpur the capital',
    selectedAnswer: null,
    answers: [],
  },
  {
    number: 8,
    answered: false,
    question: 'Which country is Kuala Lumpur the capital',
    selectedAnswer: null,
    answers: [],
  },
  {
    number: 9,
    answered: false,
    question: 'Which country is Kuala Lumpur the capital',
    selectedAnswer: null,
    answers: [],
  },
  {
    number: 10,
    answered: false,
    question: 'Which country is Kuala Lumpur the capital',
    selectedAnswer: null,
    answers: [],
  },
];
